<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">redir</string>
    <string name="this_is_first_practical_work" translatable="false">Practice Num 3</string>
    <string name="i_want_to_teleport">Drop me</string>
    <string name="completed_sheesh">gemini.google.com</string>
    <string name="error_accessing_file">Error accessing file</string>
    <string name="droplinear">drop to linear layout</string>
    <string name="dropframe">drop to frame layout</string>
    <string name="toContinue">Start</string>
    <string name="introduction">Large Language Models (LLMs) operate through a complex interplay of statistical modeling, neural network architectures, and massive datasets. Their functionality can be broadly dissected into the following core components:</string>
    <string name="core_text">
        <b>1. Tokenization and Embedding:</b> Input text is initially decomposed into smaller units called tokens.
        These tokens can represent words, sub-words, or even individual characters, depending on the specific model\'s vocabulary.
        Each token is then mapped to a high-dimensional vector, known as an embedding. This embedding represents the token\'s semantic meaning and contextual relationships with other tokens, learned during the training phase.
        The embedding space is a continuous vector space where semantically similar tokens cluster together.
        \n\n<b>2. Transformer Architecture:</b> The dominant architecture underpinning modern LLMs is the Transformer.
        Unlike recurrent neural networks (RNNs), which process text sequentially, the Transformer employs a mechanism called "self-attention."
        Self-attention allows the model to weigh the importance of different tokens within a sequence relative to each other, regardless of their position in the sequence.
        This enables the model to capture long-range dependencies and contextual nuances within the text far more effectively than RNNs.
        The Transformer architecture typically consists of multiple stacked "layers." Each layer comprises two sub-layers: a multi-head self-attention mechanism and a feed-forward neural network.
        \n\n<b>3. Multi-Head Self-Attention:</b> Within each self-attention layer, the input embeddings are linearly projected into three separate matrices: Query (Q), Key (K), and Value (V).
        Attention scores are computed by taking the dot product of the Query matrix with the transpose of the Key matrix.
        These scores are then scaled and normalized using a softmax function, producing a probability distribution that represents the attention weights assigned to each token.
        These weights determine the influence each token has on the representation of every other token in the sequence.
        The "multi-head" aspect refers to performing this process multiple times with different learned linear projections, allowing the model to capture different aspects of the relationships between tokens.
        The outputs of each "head" are then concatenated and linearly projected again.
        \n\n<b>4. Feed-Forward Network:</b> Following the self-attention mechanism, each token\'s representation is passed through a position-wise feed-forward neural network.
        This network typically consists of two linear transformations with a non-linear activation function (e.g., ReLU or GeLU) in between.
        This component adds further non-linearity and allows the model to learn more complex representations.
        \n\n<b>5. Layer Stacking and Residual Connections:</b> Multiple Transformer layers are stacked sequentially.
        Each layer refines the representation of the tokens, building upon the context and relationships captured by previous layers.
        Residual connections (adding the input of a layer to its output) and layer normalization are employed to improve training stability and gradient flow, allowing for the training of very deep networks.
        \n\n<b>6. Pre-training and Fine-tuning:</b> LLMs are typically trained in two phases.
        Pre-training involves training the model on a massive dataset of text and code, often scraped from the internet.
        The model learns to predict the next token in a sequence (autoregressive language modeling) or to reconstruct masked tokens (masked language modeling).
        This phase allows the model to learn general-purpose language representations and statistical patterns in the data.
        Fine-tuning adapts the pre-trained model to a specific downstream task, such as text generation, translation, or question answering.
        This is done by training the model on a smaller, task-specific dataset.
        \n\n<b>7. Output Generation:</b> During inference (text generation), the model processes an input prompt (a sequence of tokens).
        The model\'s output is a probability distribution over its entire vocabulary, representing the likelihood of each token being the next token in the sequence.
        A decoding algorithm (e.g., greedy decoding, beam search, top-k sampling) is then used to select the most probable sequence of tokens to generate the output text.
        The model generates text one token at a time, conditioning each new token on the previously generated tokens and the input prompt.
        The final output is constructed token-by-token, using the context generated up to that point to inform all subsequent generation.
    </string>
    <string name="to_frame">to frame</string>
    <string name="home">home</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="to_linear">to linear</string>
    <string name="login">Log in</string>
    <string name="password">password</string>
    <string name="username">username</string>
    <string name="extra_content_hello">Welcome to the extra private content that nobody seen</string>
    <string name="see_extra">See Private Content</string>
    <string name="extra_2">Nix, the adorable, furry, and undeniably fierce companion of Kay Vess in Star Wars Outlaws, hails from a fascinating, albeit somewhat mysterious, corner of the galaxy. He\'s a Merqaal, a species not widely known in the mainstream Star Wars universe, making him a bit of a novelty.
        \n\nImagine a creature that blends the best features of a loyal dog, a stealthy cat, and maybe even a touch of a mischievous monkey. That starts to paint a picture of Nix. His history is largely tied to his bond with Kay. They\'re more than just partners; they\'re a team forged in the underworld\'s fires. It is said that Nix and Kay found each other, and it wouldn\'t be too much off to say that rescued each other, likely during one of Kay\'s many escapades or close calls. The specifics of their first meeting are a story yet to be fully told, adding to their mystique.
        \n\n<b>Nix,</b> as a Merqaal, is perfectly adapted to the life of a scoundrel\'s companion. He\'s small and agile, able to squeeze into tight spaces, scout ahead, distract enemies, and even retrieve objects. This agility is coupled with surprising strength and ferocity when needed. While he might look cute and cuddly, Nix is not to be underestimated. He\'s got sharp claws and teeth and an unwavering loyalty to Kay, making him a formidable ally in a fight or a handy helper in a heist.
        \n\nThe Merqaal species itself is somewhat shrouded in mystery. We only know a little, however, we know that they come from a harsh desert world. As a species, they are very loyal.
    </string>
    <string name="listItemExample">Open ListView Example</string>
    <string name="recyclerViewText" translatable="false" />
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">hi</string>
    <string name="name" translatable="false" />
    <string name="type_something">type something</string>

</resources>